Very interesting. Is there anyone else in here?
I don't think so. It's a mass.
It says, "You're so good with water.
He can handle water so well.
Cute.
Looks like fun.
Yes, they are.
Well, this time, the five of us are together for the first time in a long time at Hajimete Gakuen.
Long time no see.
It's been so long!
How have you been?
I've been fine.
I missed you.
What's going on?
It's really tough on these kids.
They're really tough.
I can handle the back two, but...
But I can't control three of them.
Their faces are all over the place.
Who is?
But Yuzuki's circle just did it right before we started.
That's right.
You were copying him.
He was doing it like a motivator.
I have to do my best to keep everyone together today.
Please do.
Here.
Tahmimin folks, this channel... it's a channel, isn't it?
Program.
I have something to say to those of you who are watching this program
Yes, sir.
Actually, these four students will be graduating from the Junkanoo Academy!
Yay!
They are graduating!
I've worn this uniform a lot.
I really did.
I could only wear it like this.
You did?
Junior high school. I graduated.
I see. You prepared it for this show.
Yes!
The Hajime Gakuen uniform.
I didn't know that.
But, you know, you wore it a lot.
So a few more shows? Two more times? I can wear it.
Oh, yeah.
Just in time for the 100th anniversary of the Junky Junky Academy.
Oh!
You predicted it 100 times.
Million!
MILLIONS.
But you know what, guys?
Uh, no.
We didn't do that many.
Million isn't on the air.
Yes, it is.
But all of you Tahmins have been watching us for a long time.
100 times.
We've been able to continue. Thank you again.
Now that that's all settled, let's take a look back at the past broadcasts of "Junkanoo Gakuen" together.
First of all, I would like to share with you what kind of content we have aired so far.
I have a list of what we have broadcasted so far, up to 1997, I think.
That's a lot.
So many memories!
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing.
It's always under like the summary section of the video.
It's a compilation of sentences from the comments.
I can feel the love in the beautiful sentences.
The staff of Hajime-chan Academy
Nobu wrote it.
He's a great guy.
Bungsai, you wrote it.
He is really the one and only Bunsai, and he has not been able to make it all the way through the broadcast, but he has been able to make it all the way through the broadcast.
But it was more interesting and full of originality.
It's very interesting and original.
It makes me want to see it. It makes me want to see it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The 10th and last one... are you listening to me? Ho-chan...
You're getting a lot of attention.
I know. You're curious, aren't you?
You weren't listening to me.
I was listening. I really was.
Look at it from your point of view. Sorry, Nobu.
I'm sorry, Nobu.
I can feel the staff's love for me.
I'm sure you all have your own memories of the show.
Do you have any memorable episodes?
There are many!Lots of it!
Eh, but I did it remotely!
Um, yes, there was a remote and everything. This was recorded. You did it!
What are you squeezing? What's wrong? Maru!
Maru! You're joking!
You know, we were playing Shiritori at home!
Yeah, that's why I found out where Marumi lives.
I saw it. My hairy eyes.
It's not nice to shiritori remotely!
And since I'm so knowledgeable...
I have to bring it.
That's funny.
It was fun back then.
I have a lot of fond memories of the remote.
It was fun.
It was the only time I could do it.
To keep it going through the Corona period.
Have fun.
You know, I shot this at home. The crew drove by my place.
He drove by and handed me the equipment. Oh, yeah.
Isn't that amazing? It's amazing, isn't it?
I don't know. I mean, I got the equipment, and when they were done, they put it back in the car.
I don't know where the crew was while they were doing that, but they were there for about an hour while we were trying to figure it out.
It's funny to think about where they spent their time while we were trying to find out what they were doing.
It's so funny. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
I don't know what else to do.
I don't know... but I'm going to go on and on and on and on.
I'm not sure if it's the same for all of us, but I'm sure it's the same for all of us.
I've been waiting for a long time.
I've been waiting for a long time, and I'm finally on the 16th one, and it was a remote.
I'm not sure if it was a remote or something else, but it was really interesting.
The 16th case is a pretty bad concept... and the 16th baby is the ultimate weapon of Team Killer Whale, Nao Sakura...
Baby, I'm 24 years old now, Nanami!
I want you to get to know me better.
I'm not Gian, I'm the real me
Sakura Nao thorough pursuit I'll do a profile on everything!
What a bunch of nonsense!
Let's see... I'm good at things I don't like.
I'll send it to the next plate.
Oh, it's Yuzuki's plate.
I'm a Gian, aren't I?
But I'm a spoiled brat. I'll take care of you.
Wait, wait, wait.
What kind of makeup is that?
I have no idea. It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
I don't get it. Baby's 16th period ears...
I don't understand... how is it that 16th period is so baby?
Yeah, it's really funny. You're so confident.
He's a genius!
Finally! Here he is!
I'd like to look back on this.
It's so different from what we're doing now. I don't remember. I can't remember.
I can't remember. I just know I'm Gian.
I'm not sure if I'm Gian or Baby or what.
But you're cute. Yuzu has red hair.
Oh, it's Maru! It's Maru!
Maru! Maru's here!
Maru's here again!
It's true... we're dancing at this time.
Maru's here.
So cute!
You used to have short hair. You've grown it long.
You've changed a lot. You look different.
Have you grown your bangs longer, Nanami? Bangs... So short.
That's a change, isn't it?
Anything else?
Well, Hou-chan, is there anything you remember that caught your attention?
The school trip with Nanami and Haru.
Wood Design Park in Okazaki.
That was fun.
Fishing and barbecuing.
Glamping.
and glamping.
I didn't know we could do that.
It was your first time going to a forest school like that, wasn't it?
Yes, it was the first time we went outside.
It was a secret, wasn't it?
Nami was like, "I can't put on ear drops." Oh, that's right!
Oh, yeah! She was so scared that Nanami couldn't even touch the earwax with her bare hands, while the two of us were surprisingly fine with it.
No, no, no! It was a funny contrast, wasn't it?
No! They're amazing! They touch earwaters, they touch crabs, they're wild children!
Wild! And I can see it. I can see the earwax.
Oh, live earwax?
Live earwax. Because, you know, like a mill worm or something.
That's not something a girl with this hair would do!
Sure it is! Fifty year olds, this story.
That was really awesome! Yes, fishing from here.
Haru-chan was showing her talent for fishing. It was amazing, wasn't it? As expected. Haru was fishing all the time.Haru-chan was showing off her fishing talent. It was amazing, wasn't it? That's for sure. Haru was fishing all the time.
But I had never really tried river fishing. I heard you can't fish at all. Yes, this is the place. Then, miraculously, it happened. Oh, I'm so excited.
It was amazing. Really? If we catch it now, it'll be like that. It was like a cartoon.
It was really cute.
It was so cute.
I want to catch crabs!
I couldn't catch any crabs, so I was the one who was looking for crabs.
They were so cute.
So many crabs.
I got fish!
That was fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
After that, we went into the glamping room,
We all had some kind of quiz.
We had to choose between two options, like the ultimate choice.
It was fun. Sounds like fun.
We had a great time.
I miss it.
It's easy to do.
Because the 25th string, the first sentence of the current forest school chapter, you know.
The 25th string of Hachamucha Gakuen says "Youth.
Seishun.
Nobu. Nobu.
So you know about Seishun.
I see.
It's really interesting to see what happens next. Read it, read it, read it.
The second installment of the "Wai Wai Cai" romantic girls' talk. Hey, hey, what's a love banter back in school days?
What is it? I'll try to ask you that once. It's so funny.
This is Nobu's opinion too, right?
Yes!
Next time, Seishun and Haru-chan will be showing a lot of heart. Ride with me. Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
Crikey!
Wow! I'm so excited! I can't listen to this!
You couldn't listen, really.
I can't listen to this.
Oh, it's so funny.
Oh, it was too funny.
This room is so cute.
I love it.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was girl talk, wasn't it?
Talking about my favorite things.
It's amazing. There were times like this.
How about you, Haru-chan?
It was a memorable episode. Well, Haru had a lot of fun on location with Nanami, so I talked to her.
I talked to her. We had all the members together, but it was the first time we were alone together since the Sweets, you know, the Rokipan show that we did before the start of this hachimaya gakuen, so I think we were able to show how good we were then.
That's right.
Twenty-seven?
You know, East Prasn.
Ogasawara.
I don't read texts anymore.
Read it, Ma-chan.
Kizuna Eye.
This time, Hajimete Gakuen experiences the old days
Mousou Gyaru appeared on the scene in 1957
Haru-chan introduces the integration tone
Mousou gal.
Haru-chan has already become a delusional gal
That's the first time I've been told that.
It's really funny. It's really funny.
It's amazing.
Nanami's outfit and Shiba's color...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I fell in love with it before we started shooting.
I was blown away by the opening.
I wonder if this is the delusional gal...
And here, after this... No, no, after this...
There's a place in the back with some history.
It's cute, isn't it?
I'm delusional. I'm delusional.
We improvised something about our elementary school days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I knew it!
Laughs.
LOL!
This is not good.
It's the tone.
Good morning
Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning.
The staff...
A little.
I'm firm.
Ayanan!
I'm done with the prints.
I quit.
Wait a minute!
No prints!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
Can I do my makeup now?
I'm going to be decorated.
Hang on tight.
Hiya, sweetie.
Wait a minute!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Your hair's falling out like crazy.
Is it falling out?
It's falling out.
Did you just stand in the back and watch us?
The man at the shelter.
Oh, my God.
They've been there since before the first one.
He's been showing us around.
Oh, of course.
No, but... yes.
Yes, yes.
I've had a few surprises in a row, you know, after a place like this.
A raving fair.
Oh, yes.
It was a great rave fair, like a quiz, like a roller coaster, but not at all.
That's right.
I couldn't roll it, right?
That was pretty time-consuming, too.
There was a rave fair, wasn't there?
Yes, we did. Last summer?
Last summer.
About a summer ago.
Yeah, yeah. You ran.
Yes, I was running.
Surprise run. Surprise run. You were fast, weren't you? You were running hard, weren't you? He ran well.
The cameraman, for example, was wearing a running outfit. I saw that. Sone-kun.
It says "Sone-kun" on it, your name. Here, in the summary section. Sone, who is in his first year with the company, is holding the camera.
The angle of view is like a documentary. It's amazing.
He was taking pictures of the staff moving from one place to another all the time.
The staff was dropping out of the film. They were running.
They were running, it was in the middle of summer. I was so sweaty, and then when we had a live show, I had to go in for one all because I was so sweaty.
There it was! I was so sweaty, I had to take off my makeup. I was recalcitrant.
That's right. There it was.
It's impossible otherwise.
It was really messy.
Yes, it was a little bit crazy that day.
It's like, this is a clownishness, you know?
Like a suspect.
What do you mean?
What is this?
Shocking.
You've got such a sharp voice, don't you?
That was so good.
Very good.
Don't say that.
When I went to school, the other kids looked like this before makeup.
That's right.
And this one, that one? Wait a minute.
Did he carry you on his back? Later.
I'm running a little late.
I'm being questioned.
Yeah, I noticed.
That's why you're in the chair.
That's why the kid's here.
If you're in make-up,
What, did you commit a crime? So, am I free to do what I want?
I'm free to do what I want.
It's fun.
It's fun. It's more than that.
It's more than enough. I wish something would come in here and there.
It's different. It's cute. I'm glad.
That was great. It's so funny.
I don't have anything to do with that leg. It's funny.
I think Momochan is going to start running. Running?
I'll start running. You definitely don't look like you're going to run.
No, really. Oh, I see. So you ran in this.
There were a lot of customers, you know.
There were a lot of customers, and we were running through a very busy place.
I was surprised.
You only changed your shoes.
Yes.
The cameraman was amazing, too.
Yeah, he didn't have a camera.
Running.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Everyone's driving.
Yes, everyone is driving.
You were looking for Ho-chan, weren't you, with a car like this?
Yes, I was looking for you.
I was looking for you.I was looking for you.
I wonder where he's running.
What happened to you?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But isn't he going pretty fast? Fast.
Fast, fast, fast.
Yeah, yeah.
There's some kind of signal.
We're at a mountain crossing.
Yeah, that's it. We've been running for, what, 20 minutes?
Yeah. You don't want to run too fast because you never know where you might lose time because of the traffic lights.
I see. It's more than the altitude.
That's true.
It was hot just standing there, wasn't it? It was hot.
We ran.
You think they're coming?
What? What? Is he coming? Is he coming?
Aah!
Oh! He's back!
Good job!
Good, good, good!
It's good to be back.
I knew the marathon would bring back some memories.
Of course you remember.
Yes, of course.
When you ran the marathon.
That's right!
Speaking of marathons, there was the Nishio Marathon! Oh, yeah!
How many times have you run the Nishio Marathon? Nishio Marathon. It was so windy, wasn't it?
It was so windy. When was that? Nishio is...
Nishio is... but was it winter?
March! March!
Last year? It was cold last year...
38th period! 38th period! Before 38?
That's early! It's early!
It's 2022!
Remember the first time we all got together in the studio for a quiz? Christmas party!
Right after that! Was it?
That long ago? Surprisingly long time.
Yeah...
I'll be there with my matcha mask! I'll be waiting for you!
I get so nervous before a live feed! What's that? You guys were dancing behind me!
You want some green tea! You're so free! Oh! The show has started! Yeah! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Yeah! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Here! There it is!
They're doing something! They're doing something!
They're doing something!
Fluffy people!
They're so cute!
Dan is so cute!
He's so cute!
Hey!
This is the course!
Yeah! We all wore these masks!
That's right! They were so cute!
They were so cute!
Oh man, I can't get used to this mask.
It's so dark. I guess it's matcha.
Dark matcha.
You've been delivering the show for a long time.
We stood at various points, and we were there to give you a live feed.
We made a cheering board.
We couldn't speak up.
Matcha!
So cute!
There were days like this. There was.
So it's the first half, rather the first half.
And the first string.
I was impressed by the first recording where all the members were together.
It was fun. It was fun.
That was the cake incident. The cake incident.
That's all I can think of.
Why?
Because the birthday of the cake was coming up, so the staff prepared our names before the cake.
It turned out to be a Christmas cake by mistake.
Because I took the wrong one.
I brought the wrong person's cake.
I didn't realize I had brought it.
I brought it even though I knew.
I should have said something.
The one I told you to tell me right now.
That's why some Christmas cake came here.
It's at some house.
Oh, yeah.
Happy birthday, Nanami and Hami.
A little bit.
It's there.
Because there's such a miracle.Because there is such a miracle.
It was really funny.
It's funny.
It's too funny. Because the staff and the personalities are too strong. It's really strong. Really.
You know, you already graduated once, right? That's right.
Yasui-san was there, too. That's right. Yasui-san. That was interesting, wasn't it?
Yasui-san. Yasui-san.
Oh, may I? The first time we were on location outside,
Yes, there was a time when we went to a hunting lodge, and at the hunting lodge,
I was told to stay there and eat the cake because they wanted to film the cake-eating scene from afar, so I was filming from behind.
But I was eating it.
But after about 5 minutes, they said OK, and I wondered why, but there was no one there, the camera had stopped, and they asked me to speak to them.
I was eating cake with a beautiful posture.
Karyasue.
Fun, fun, fun.
Great! Great!
Hey, really.
Oh, man.
This is my favorite scene.
There it is! There it is! There it is!
It's somewhere... Which one is it?
This one... this one...
And it was only used for a second.
Hey...
What's with the arcadors?
From here, too.
Oh...
Why?
Congratulations.
It's pure.
It's a nice flower-viewing party.
Introductions.
And... you know...
At this moment...
There was a moment when the contrast was really interesting.
Yes, yes, yes.
The colors are a little...
This flower...
It's all blown out to white.
It's so cute!
It's very pretty.
It's okay, but it's funny.
It's funny. It's funny.
There's a lot of stuff here.
There's a lot.
They did a lot of live shows... and they kept it all the same.
And the 10th anniversary...
Yeah, that was really good.
You know, there's a lot of behind-the-scenes extras that you can get on Blu-ray or something.
It's often included as a bonus on Blu-ray or something like that.
But to be able to watch it for free on Rokipo was really new.
It's really new.
I thought it was great.
I see. The editing is so cute, and they love each other so much.
Especially for Morochi-sama, we rehearsed outdoors and it was raining hard, so we couldn't see the rehearsal.
You can only see the rehearsal footage from here.
It's great. And the camera...
And also... you know... you can leave the camera with us now... and we can film each other... and that's exactly what Yuzuki's camera says.
That's right.
We rehearsed in costume, so getting caught in the rain would be the worst.
We were in a hurry. You were wearing your top, and Hoi was sad because his pockets were closed.
Eye drops.
I think only Paeko and Na's pockets were closed.
I'm sure they use their pockets.
I'm looking at Hoi's pockets... armour gelatine...
Just because...
Frito, ah, socialism, who cheat 3
Oh, cheat three.
It's funny, because we, the filmmakers, have been able to get in close.
I hope you think it was a great experience for the insomniacs, and we had a lot of fun doing it.
Thank you very much.
The love, the love of the staff, the love of Mr. Y, the twitter staff member who manages the twitter.
I'm sure you know that Mr. Y, who manages the twitter account, participated in all of the filming except for the two times he was on location.
Wow, that's right.
He himself is called Tahmin.
I think she's famous for it, but she was on her days off.
He was on location. But rather than taking time off, he wanted to make something good on location with all the orcas.
That's right. So last night, I received an e-mail from someone.
I was so sad to hear that a program that I loved so much, a program that I really wanted to do even if I had to take a break, was going to be canceled,
He wrote me a very long message saying how sad it was for him to lose his favorite show.
I was really on the verge of tears. There is already so much love.
I'm so glad.
Thank you so much.
I've updated the fan club.
Because, you know, when I was on location,
Oh, I just got the registration for the nativity.
Because they're going to put a little bit of Tamwin episode,
The love is really deep on a daily basis.
I'm glad to see that they've grown to love me more and more since we started working together like this.
It makes me happy.Glad to hear it.
Why did this crazy school start in the first place?
Hey!
Indeed.
Yes! I just heard that too,
Apparently, I was the one who had the proposal.
What?
That's right! Yes, I did!
What? What do you mean?
We had talked about doing some kind of show with the four orcas, but we hadn't decided what the content would be.
I wrote a big piece of paper with all kinds of ideas and submitted it, and it got accepted and I joined Ajamecha Academy.
What? Really? That's right! That's what happened!
No, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no, no! Really? I forgot too!
I forgot about the profiles and all that. I asked a lot of directors and consulted with them about what I should do to convey the cuteness of these girls.
I asked a lot of directors and consulted with them about what I should do to convey their cuteness.
I wrote a lot. I wrote a lot of words, like a lot of punching. I showed it to Mr. Nobe, consulted with him, and told him that I thought we should do something.
That's right.
That's what Nobe told me just now. He told me that it was you.
I was so happy.
You never make eye contact with me. He's turned into a shinny knob.
I've been beaten once already.
But we are very happy to know that a program that we are so attached to has continued for 100 episodes.
Thank you very much.
Well, that's all for this time.
We will have the last 100th episode, and I would like to ask you to tell us what's on your mind again.
What was that pose?
Pose with your heart in your chest.
Well, that's it for the 99th period. I hope you all enjoy the next one.
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching.